const quizquestions = [{question: "The Eiffel Tower is located where in Paris?",
  answers: ["Bois de Boulogne","Champ de Mars","Jardin des Plantes","Parc de Belleville"],
  answer: 1},
{question: "Which Apollo mission landed the first humans on the Moon?",
  answers: ["Apollo 7","Apollo 9","Apollo 11","Apollo 13"],
  answer: 2},
{question: "Who starred in the 1959 epic film 'Ben-Hur'?",
  answers: ["Charlton Heston","Clark Gable","Errol Flynn","Lee Marvin"],
  answer: 0},
{question: "What is the International Air Transport Association airport code for Heathrow Airport?",
  answers: ["HRW","HTR","LHR","LHW"],
  answer: 2},
{question: "The reactor at the site of the Chernobyl nuclear disaster is now in which country?",
  answers: ["Ukraine","Slovakia","Hungary","Russia"],
  answer: 0},
{question: "Which volcano is best known for its eruption in AD 79 that led to the destruction of the Roman cities of Pompeii and Herculaneum?",
  answers: ["Mount Etna","Mount Stromboli","Mount Vesuvius","Mount Vulture"],
  answer: 2},
{question: "The British Naval Ensign features a Union Jack in which corner?",
  answers: ["Top left","Top right","Bottom left","Bottom right"],
  answer: 0},
{question: "Which castle was the childhood home of Elizabeth Bowes-Lyon, the late Queen Mother?",
  answers: ["Craigievar Castle","Glamis Castle","Invergarry Castle","Loch Leven Castle"],
  answer: 1},
{question: "Which countries comprise The British Isles?",
    answers: ["England","England and Wales","England, Scotland and Wales","England, Scotland, Wales, Ireland"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is the name given to the part of the North Sea between Lincolnshire and Norfolk?",
    answers: ["The Fen Marshes","The Humber Estuary","The Lincolnshire Fens","The Wash"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is the capital of the Republic of Ireland?",
    answers: ["Belfast","Cork","Dublin","Galway"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the longest river (entirely) in England?",
    answers: ["Medway","Severn","Stour","Thames"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is the name of the highest peak in the Grampian Mountains?",
    answers: ["Ben Nevis","Cross Fell","Scafell Pike","Snowdon"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the name of the popular seaside resort that is 10 miles North of Lowestoft?",
    answers: ["Clacton-On-Sea","Cromer","Great Yarmouth","Skegness"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the name of the large island joined to the Welsh mainland by the Menai Bridge?",
    answers: ["Anglesey","Holyhead","Isle of Wight","Isle of Skye"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Born as Harry Webb, who became known as the 'Peter Pan of Pop'?",
    answers: ["Adam Faith","Alvin Stardust","Cliff Richard","Tom Jones"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "'I Predict A Riot' was a hit in 2005 for which pop band?",
    answers: ["Kasabian","Kaiser Chiefs","Pet Shop Boys","Take That"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Joe Strummer, Mick Jones, Topper Headon and Paul Simenon were which pop band?",
    answers: ["The Clash","The Rolling Stones","The Shadows","The Who"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Which pop group, led by Justin Hawkins, originated in Lowestoft?",
    answers: ["The Brightness","The Darkness","The Dead Of Night","The Shade"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Pop singer, guitarist and songwriter Robert Smith founded which group?",
    answers: ["The Answer","The Cure","The Remedy","The Solution"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which singer fronted the pop band Duran Duran?",
    answers: ["Martin Fry","Robert Smith","Simon Le Bon","Tony Hadley"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which pop group had numerous 1960s hits with songs written by Brian Wilson?",
    answers: ["The Four Seasons","The Kinks","The Beach Boys","Small Faces"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "From which part of Britain does the pop band Stereophonics hail?",
    answers: ["London","Scotland","Manchester","Wales"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Who recorded 'Ebony and Ivory' in 1982 with Paul McCartney?",
    answers: ["Barry White","Michael Jackson","Ray Charles","Stevie Wonder"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which pop singer starred alongside Kevin Costner in the film 'The Bodyguard'?",
    answers: ["Celine Dion","Diana Ross","Janet Jackson","Whitney Houston"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which member of The Beatles replaced previous member Pete Best?",
    answers: ["George Harrison","John Lennon","Ringo Starr","Paul McCartney"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What were the names of the two male members of pop group Abba?",
    answers: ["Benny and Leo","Bjarne and Bobby","Benny and Bjorn","Bernard and Billy"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which was Robbie Williams' first top ten solo pop single?",
    answers: ["Angels","Forever Love","Freedom","How Deep Is Your Love"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "With which American rock group did Gene Simmons play?",
    answers: ["Blue Oyster Cult","Guns 'N Roses","Kiss","Ramones"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which pop act topped the charts with 'Setting Sun' in 1996?",
    answers: ["Prodigy","The Chemical Brothers","Underworld","Orbital"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which American pop singer had hits with 'Runaway' and 'Swiss Maid'?",
    answers: ["Bobby Vee","Del Shannon","Freddy Cannon","Johnny Tillotson"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which pop group was fronted by Richard Ashcroft?",
    answers: ["The Verve","Radiohead","Pulp","Manic Street Preachers"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Orecchietta is pasta in what sort of shapes?",
    answers: ["Ears","Parcels","Spirals","Tubes"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the traditional topping on a Lancashire Hotpot?",
    answers: ["Breadcrumbs","Dumplings","Mashed Potato","Sliced Potato"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is Wasabi?",
    answers: ["Brazilian Root Vegetable","Chinese Mushroom","Hawaiian Fruit","Japanese Horseradish"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "By what name do we normally refer to the Chinese Gooseberry?",
    answers: ["Kiwi Fruit","Mango","Passion Fruit","Star Fruit"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the main ingredient of Baba Ghanoush?",
    answers: ["Aubergine","Celeriac","Courgette","Fennel"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Which herb is used to make Pesto?",
    answers: ["Basil","Dill","Mint","Tarragon"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "From what fruit is the liqueur Cr√®me De Cassis produced?",
    answers: ["Blackcurrant","Cherry","Raspberry","Sloe"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the Mexican avocado dip flavoured with lime, coriander & spice?",
    answers: ["Guacamole","Salsa","Satay","Taramasalata"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the name of the ice cream dessert which is encased in meringue?",
    answers: ["Eton Mess","Baked Alaska","Knickerbocker Glory","Tiramisu"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "From which country does Mavrud wine originate?",
    answers: ["Romania","Bulgaria","South Africa","Chile"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What gives Mead its flavour?",
    answers: ["Ginger","Mint","Honey","Rose Hips"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What nickname is often applied to an amateur radio operator?",
    answers: ["Ham","Sam","Spam","Tam"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the usual voltage used on electric model railways?",
    answers: ["6v DC","12v DC","18v DC","24v DC"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In 1913 the New York World newspaper published the first example of what type of puzzle?",
    answers: ["Sudoku","Anagram","Crossword","Wordsearch"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the name of the slot car racing brand introduced in 1961?",
    answers: ["Scalectric","Scalectrix","Scalextric","Scalextrix"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What name is given to the art of fine handwriting?",
    answers: ["Callanetics","Calligraphy","Campanology","Chiropody"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What name is given to the art of fine handwriting?",
    answers: ["Callanetics","Calligraphy","Campanology","Chiropody"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which century did the Italian painter, Titian, produce his most famous works?",
    answers: ["13th century","16th century","18th century","19th century"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which two countries fought at the Battle of Agincourt, 1415?",
    answers: ["England and France","England and Spain","France and Netherlands","France and Prussia"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "In which South American country did the Incas establish their capital?",
    answers: ["Chile","Colombia","Ecuador","Peru"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which 51-mile waterway opened to traffic in August 1914?",
    answers: ["Manchester Ship Canal","Panama Canal","St Lawrence Seaway","Suez Canal"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which country was attacked by the Soviet Union on 30 November 1939?",
    answers: ["Denmark","Finland","Norway","Poland"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which country was partitioned by Austria, Russia and Prussia throughout the 1800s?",
    answers: ["Finland","Poland","Romania","Switzerland"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which European country was ruled by Francisco Franco between 1939 and 1975?",
    answers: ["Italy","Malta","Portugal","Spain"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "How was the 'Kingdom of Serbs, Croats and Slovenes' re-named in 1929?",
    answers: ["Bulgaria","Czechoslovakia","Romania","Yugoslavia"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "How is the line of zero degrees longitude commonly known?",
    answers: ["Arctic Circle","Equator","Greenwich Meridian","Tropic Of Cancer"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What word describes a very deep and narrow river valley?",
    answers: ["Canyon","Ravine","Rift","Vale"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What lines on maps join points of similar height?",
    answers: ["Bridle paths","Contour lines","Grid references","Isobars"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What stretch of a river is the final stage before reaching the river mouth?",
    answers: ["Channel","Delta","Estuary","Tributary"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What makes a pine cone open and close?",
    answers: ["Temperature","Light","Humidity","Atmospheric pressure"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which gas is the most prevalent in the atmosphere?",
    answers: ["Oxygen","Nitrogen","Carbon dioxide","Hydrogen"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "The Tropic of Cancer is where?",
    answers: ["North of the Equator","South of the Equator","On the Equator","Both sides of the Equator"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "From which country does Samba music originate?",
    answers: ["Spain","Argentina","Cuba","Brazil"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "'Orpheus In The Underworld' included which famous dance music?",
    answers: ["Bolero","Bossa Nova","Can-Can","Charleston"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What timing is used in Foxtrot dance music?",
    answers: ["3/4","4/4","4/8","7/8"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "During which Eurovision Song Contest was 'Riverdance' first performed?",
    answers: ["1986","1990","1994","1998"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who composed 'The Nutcracker'?",
    answers: ["Beethoven","Handel","Tchaikovsky","Mozart"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which dinosaur's name means 'roof lizard'?",
    answers: ["Pteradactyl","Stegosaurus","Triceratops","Tyrannosaurus"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which football club moved to Milton Keynes to eventually form 'MK Dons'?",
    answers: ["Gloucester United FC","St Leonards FC","Telford United FC","Wimbledon FC"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Blue Mountain Coffee comes from where?",
    answers: ["Colombia","Costa Rica","Jamaica","Kenya"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Blue Mountain Coffee comes from where?",
    answers: ["Colombia","Costa Rica","Jamaica","Kenya"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In the bible, who was found in a basket amongst the bullrushes?",
    answers: ["Joseph","Jonah","Levi","Moses"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    answers: ["Auckland","Christchurch","Tauranga","Wellington"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is the capital of New Zealand?",
    answers: ["Auckland","Christchurch","Tauranga","Wellington"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Who performed 'Maybellene', 'Roll over Beethoven', 'Rock and Roll Music' and 'Johnny B Goode' during the 1950s?",
    answers: ["B B King","Chuck Berry","Fats Domino","Ray Charles"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Who performed 'Maybellene', 'Roll over Beethoven', 'Rock and Roll Music' and 'Johnny B Goode' during the 1950s?",
    answers: ["Jerry Lee Lewis","Chuck Berry","Fats Domino","Ray Charles"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which film does an English teacher tell the students that they may call him 'O Captain! My Captain!''?",
    answers: ["Dead Poets Society","Educating Rita","Good Will Hunting","The Graduate"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Where is the largest expanse of medieval stained glass in the world?",
    answers: ["Lincoln Cathedral","Sistine Chapel","York Minster","Westminster Cathedral"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which is the only Portuguese speaking country in the Americas?",
    answers: ["Argentina","Columbia","Brazil","Peru"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which is the only Portuguese speaking country in the Americas?",
    answers: ["Argentina","Columbia","Brazil","Peru"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "How many keys does a modern piano have?",
    answers: ["85","86","87","88"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "In a rainbow, what colour is the outer part of the arch?",
    answers: ["Orange","Red","Violet","Yellow"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which chambers in a human heart collect blood from an atrium?",
    answers: ["Barnacles","Chronicles","Clavicles","Ventricles"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "In Greek and Roman mythology, a multi-headed hound which guards the gates of Hades is called what?",
    answers: ["Barabas","Cerberus","Pluto","Echidna"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Who is the King of the Gods in Greek Mythology?",
    answers: ["Apollo","Dionysus","Poseidon","Zeus"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "A squirrel's nest is called a what?",
    answers: ["Eyrie","Drey","Form","Sett"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What is Harry's surname in the 'Dirty Harry' film series?",
    answers: ["Carnegie","Callahan","Colt","Crown"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "David Howell Evans is more widely known by which stage name?",
    answers: ["The Cliff","The Edge","The Line","The Wall"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Sports car manufacturer Ferrari are based where?",
    answers: ["Madrid, Spain","Malmo, Sweden","Maranello, Italy","Montevideo, Uruguay"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Sports car manufacturer Ferrari are based where?",
    answers: ["Madrid, Spain","Malmo, Sweden","Maranello, Italy","Montevideo, Uruguay"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who is 'Ben', as sung by Michael Jackson?",
    answers: ["His pet rat","His pet dog","His brother","His imaginary friend"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "In 'The Wizard of Oz' what is the name of the Good Witch?",
    answers: ["Gaynor","Glenda","Glinda","Gloria"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who portrayed the character 'Max Headroom'?",
    answers: ["Arnold Schwarzenegger","Christopher Lambert","Harrison Ford","Matt Frewer"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "In which American state is Lake Allatoona?",
    answers: ["Alabama","Colorado","Delaware","Georgia"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "In Star Trek, what is Captain Kirk's middle name?",
    answers: ["Tadleigh","Taliesin","Tiberius","Thaddeus"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What does 'Hong Kong' translate to in English?",
    answers: ["Happy Island","Fragrant Harbour","High Peak","Land of Wealth"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which year did Channel 4 begin broadcasting in the UK?",
    answers: ["1972","1977","1982","1987"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In which service did John F Kennedy serve during World War Two?",
    answers: ["United States Air Force","United States Army","United States Marine Corps","United States Navy"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Dry air contains roughly what percentage of nitrogen by volume?",
    answers: ["28","38","58","78"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which character was lacking a heart in 'The Wizard of Oz'?",
    answers: ["The Lion","The Scarecrow","The Tin Man","Toto"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "The Battle of Trafalgar was fought off the south-west coast of which country?",
    answers: ["England","Italy","Spain","Sweden"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who lives in Hundred Acre Wood?",
    answers: ["Basil Brush","Rupert the Bear","Winnie the Pooh","Paddington Bear"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the medical term for lockjaw?",
    answers: ["Mumps","Rubella","Tetanus","Smallpox"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What sport is played at Hogwarts?",
    answers: ["Quadrant","Quicket","Quoits","Quidditch"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Who voiced the cartoon character Bugs Bunny?",
    answers: ["Dan Castellaneta","Don Messick","Joseph Barbera","Mel Blanc"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Scurvy is a disease resulting from a deficiency of what?",
    answers: ["Vitamin A","Vitamin B","Vitamin C","Vitamin D"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Quadrophenia is the sixth studio album by which English rock band?",
    answers: ["The Rolling Stones","The Who","The Jam","The Clash"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which of these London parks has no lakes?",
    answers: ["Green Park","Hyde Park","Regent's Park","St James's Park"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is Arnold Schwarzenegger's middle name?",
    answers: ["Alan","Albert","Alfred","Alois"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which football club has the nickname 'The Blades'?",
    answers: ["Scunthorpe United","Sheffield United","Sheffield Wednesday","Southampton"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Hypophosphatasia affects what part of the body?",
    answers: ["Blood","Bones","Muscles","Nerves"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which of these colours is not a primary colour?",
    answers: ["Red","Blue","Green","Yellow"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What was the name of the Skye Terrier whose statue stands near his master's grave in Edinburgh?",
    answers: ["Blackfriars Bobby","Greenfriars Bobby","Greyfriars Bobby","Whitefriars Bobby"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the collective noun for a group of cats?",
    answers: ["A chowder","A clowder","A crowder","A herd"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "The Manx cat is often born without what?",
    answers: ["Claws","Hair","A tail","Whiskers"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In Alice in Wonderland, what is the name of the cat that can appear and disappear at will?",
    answers: ["Derbyshire Cat","Cheshire Cat","Lancashire Cat","Yorkshire Cat"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In Alice in Wonderland, what is the name of the cat that can appear and disappear at will?",
    answers: ["Derbyshire Cat","Cheshire Cat","Lancashire Cat","Yorkshire Cat"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which year was the film 'Jurassic Park' released?",
    answers: ["1992","1993","1994","1995"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which actor appeared alongside Tom Cruise in 'A Few Good Men'?",
    answers: ["Al Pacino","Dustin Hoffman","Jack Nicholson","Michael Douglas"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the location of London's National Gallery?",
    answers: ["Grosvenor Square","Leicester Square","Sloane Square","Trafalgar Square"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Vincent van Gogh produced a series of still life paintings depicting which flowers?",
    answers: ["Daffodils","Geraniums","Sunflowers","Tulips"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "The English artist George Stubbs, who died in 1806, is best known for his paintings of what?",
    answers: ["Cats","Deer","Dogs","Horses"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which founding father of communism was a German philosopher?",
    answers: ["Che Guevara","Karl Marx","Keir Hardy","Leon Trotsky"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "At what time each day is the famous Edinburgh cannon fired?",
    answers: ["11:00am","12:00 noon","1:00pm","2:00pm"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In which European country is the city of Salzburg?",
    answers: ["Austria","Czech Republic","Germany","Switzerland"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Into which sea does the River Danube flow?",
    answers: ["Baltic Sea","Black Sea","Mediterranean Sea","North Sea"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which European country is denoted by the letters 'CH' on motor vehicles?",
    answers: ["Croatia","Czech Republic","Switzerland","Denmark"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which UK political party did Prime Minister Clement Attlee lead?",
    answers: ["Conservative","Labour","Liberal","Social Democrat"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What was the Spanish unit of currency before the introduction of the Euro in 2002?",
    answers: ["Escudo","Peseta","Peso","Real"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "The stiletto heel takes its name from what?",
    answers: ["A needle","An icicle","A dagger","A poker"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "The Hugo Boss fashion house is based in which country?",
    answers: ["Italy","Germany","Switzerland","USA"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "The Hugo Boss fashion house is based in which country?",
    answers: ["Italy","Germany","Switzerland","USA"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What colour is the background of signs to tourist attractions in the UK?",
    answers: ["Blue","Brown","White","Yellow"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which British city are the headquarters of the Driver and Vehicle Licensing Agency?",
    answers: ["London","Birmingham","Swansea","Manchester"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "The 1999 film The Green Mile is set during which decade?",
    answers: ["1930s","1950s","1970s","1990s"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "The title of the 1978 film Midnight Express is prison slang for what?",
    answers: ["Escape attempt","Food parcel","Prison visit","Solitary confinement"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Who directed the 1990 film Edward Scissorhands?",
    answers: ["Steven Speilberg","Chris Columbus","Tim Burton","Quentin Tarantino"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who won the first series of UK Celebrity Big Brother in 2001?",
    answers: ["Jack Dee","Chris Eubank","Claire Sweeney","Anthea Turner"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the title of Big Brother's theme tune, released as a single in 2000?",
    answers: ["Element One","Element Two","Element Three","Element Four"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "How many couples took part in each episode of TV's 'Generation Game'?",
    answers: ["2","3","4","5"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which game show started the catchphrase 'Come On Down' in 1984?",
    answers: ["Game For A Laugh","My Kind Of Music","Supermarket Sweep","The Price Is Right"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which 1990s sitcom, set in California, starred comic actor Will Smith?",
    answers: ["Cheers","Fresh Prince Of Bel-Air","Saved By The Bell","Seinfeld"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What is the surname of 'Frasier' in the TV sitcom of the same name?",
    answers: ["Craig","Crane","Craven","Cray"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which part of London was the sitcom 'Only Fools And Horses' set?",
    answers: ["Balham","Clapham","Lewisham","Peckham"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which Simpsons character uses the catchphrase 'Okily Dokily'?",
    answers: ["Dr Hibbert","Ned Flanders","Sideshow Bob","Brandine Spuckler"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What is the name of Mr Burns's assistant in The Simpsons?",
    answers: ["Smith","Smithers","Symington","Smythe"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which city is the TV sitcom 'Friends' set?",
    answers: ["Boston","Chicago","Los Angeles","New York"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which part did Ron Howard play in the TV sitcom 'Happy Days'?",
    answers: ["Howard Cunningham","Fonzie","Ralph Malph","Richie Cunningham"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which part did Ron Howard play in the TV sitcom 'Happy Days'?",
    answers: ["Howard Cunningham","Fonzie","Ralph Malph","Richie Cunningham"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which British TV soap was first screened on Friday 9th December 1960?",
    answers: ["Brookside","Coronation Street","Eastenders","Emmerdale Farm"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which former EastEnders actress appeared in the film 'Love Actually'?",
    answers: ["June Brown","Martine McCutcheon","Pam St Clement","Wendy Richard"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "'Royle Family' stars Sue Johnston and Ricky Tomlinson appeared in which TV soap?",
    answers: ["Brookside","EastEnders","Emmerdale","Home And Away"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the name of the coffee shop used by the characters in the sitcom 'Friends'?",
    answers: ["Bean Town","Central Perk","Grounds Swell","Sunbucks"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Whom did Jennifer Aniston marry in 2000?",
    answers: ["Matt Damon","Ben Affleck","Brad Pitt","Johnny Depp"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "The US sitcom 'Frasier' is set in which city?",
    answers: ["Boston","Chicago","New York","Seattle"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which group's first 7 singles charted at number 1 in the UK?",
    answers: ["The Beatles","Abba","The Spice Girls","Boyzone"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Andrew Ridgeley formed one half of which UK pop duo?",
    answers: ["Erasure","Hall & Oates","Wham!","The Pet Shop Boys"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which of these US artists have never topped the UK singles charts?",
    answers: ["Eminem","Tina Turner","Stevie Wonder","Justin Timberlake"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which Neil Diamond penned song reached number 1 in the UK charts in 1967?",
    answers: ["Sweet Caroline","Forever In Blue Jeans","I'm A Believer","Love On The Rocks"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which year was the film 'Titanic' released?",
    answers: ["1993","1997","2001","2005"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which year was the film 'Titanic' released?",
    answers: ["1993","1997","2001","2005"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which artist sang the song '‚Äú'Oh, Pretty Woman' from the film 'Pretty Woman'?",
    answers: ["George Harrison","Roy Orbison","Frank Sinatra","Elvis Costello"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Who voice the Genie character in the 1992 animated film Aladdin?",
    answers: ["Tom Hanks","Jim Carrey","Robin Williams","Jon Goodman"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which football club play at Elland Road?",
    answers: ["Sheffield Wednesday","Leeds United","Oldham","Burnley"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Approximately how many Earths would fit inside the Sun?",
    answers: ["100","10,000","100,000","1,000,000"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Anemophobia is the fear of what?",
    answers: ["Spiders","The dark","Fire","Wind"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "The name of which spice comes from the French word for ‚Äònail‚Äô?",
    answers: ["Cinnamon","Cardamom","Clove","Cumin"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In Alice‚Äôs Adventures in Wonderland, which game was played by the Queen of Hearts using hedgehogs as balls?",
    answers: ["Quintet","Croquet","Quidditch","Polo"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which is the largest internal organ in the human body?",
    answers: ["Heart","Lung","Liver","Brain"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What was defined as ‚Äòthree grains of barley, dry and round, placed end to end lengthwise‚Äô?",
    answers: ["Centimetre","Millimetre","Inch","Link"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who was the prime minister of the UK at the time of Queen Elizabeth II‚Äôs coronation?",
    answers: ["Neville Chamberlain","Winston Churchill","Harold McMillan","Anthony Eden"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which present-day country was the Battle of Waterloo fought?",
    answers: ["France","England","Belgium","Netherlands"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which religion is most commonly practiced in India?",
    answers: ["Islam","Sikhism","Hinduism","Buddhism"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which religion is most commonly practiced in India?",
    answers: ["Islam","Sikhism","Hinduism","Buddhism"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which are the only big cats to have a tuft or bunch of hair at the end of their tail?",
    answers: ["Tigers","Lions","Leopards","Jaguars"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "If you were a cartographer, what would you be studying?",
    answers: ["Stamps","Postcards","Maps","Geology"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In which country is the game Chess believed to have originated in the 7th century?",
    answers: ["Spain","Russia","India","China"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which English team became known as 'The Invincibles' after winning the league undefeated in 2004?",
    answers: ["Chelsea","Manchester United","Arsenal","Liverpool"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which sportsman's birth name was 'Cassius Clay'?",
    answers: ["Michael Jordan","Muhammad Ali","Hank Aaron","Joe Montana"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which Irish band had hits with 'Zombie' and 'Dreams' in the 1990s?",
    answers: ["U2","Westlife","The Cranberries","B*Witched"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who won the first UK X Factor in 2004?",
    answers: ["Shayne Ward","Matt Cardle","Leona Lewis","Steve Brookstein"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Who won the first UK Pop Idol in 2001?",
    answers: ["Gareth Gates","Michelle McManus","Will Young","Susan Boyle"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which of these actors did not play one of the main characters in 'Friends'?",
    answers: ["Jennifer Aniston","Courtney Love","Matthew Perry","David Schwimmer"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which actor is famous for the line 'Go ahead, make my day'?",
    answers: ["Bruce Willis","Clint Eastwood","Arnold Schwarzenegger","Sylvester Stallone"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In which ocean is the Republic of Madagascar?",
    answers: ["Atlantic","Indian","Pacific","Southern"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which sign of the zodiac comes between Leo and Libra?",
    answers: ["Virgo","Taurus","Aries","Capricorn"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Which nuts are used to make marzipan?",
    answers: ["Walnuts","Chestnuts","Almonds","Hazlenuts"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who is 'Reginald Kenneth Dwight' better known as?",
    answers: ["David Bowie","Mick Jagger","Elton John","Phil Collins"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is the world's longest river?",
    answers: ["Amazon","Yangtze","Nile","Congo"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "Which of these British cities do not have an underground rail system?",
    answers: ["Newcastle","Glasgow","Manchester","Liverpool"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which actor has won the most Oscars since the first awards in 1929?",
    answers: ["Jack Nicholson","Katharine Hepburn","Daniel Day-Lewis","Meryl Streep"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Who directed the Lord of the Rings trilogy?",
    answers: ["Steven Spielberg","James Cameron","Peter Jackson","Ron Howard"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which heavyweight boxing champion finished his career of 49 fights undefeated?",
    answers: ["Muhammad Ali","Rocky Marciano","Sugar Ray Robinson","Joe Louis"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which chess piece can only move diagonally?",
    answers: ["Queen","King","Bishop","Rook"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What flavour is Cointreau?",
    answers: ["Lemon","Raspberry","Orange","Blackcurrant"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who famously said 'Nationalism is an infantile disease. It is the measles of mankind'?",
    answers: ["Winston Churchill","Albert Einstein","Isaac Newton","JK Rowling"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Who famously said 'Nationalism is an infantile disease. It is the measles of mankind'?",
    answers: ["Winston Churchill","Albert Einstein","Isaac Newton","JK Rowling"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "The quote 'forgive your enemies but never forget their names' is attributed to which US president?",
    answers: ["George W Bush","John F Kennedy","Bill Clinton","Donald Trump"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "In 'Toy Story', Woody and Buzz Lightyear are Andy's toys. Who is the next door neighbour that they fear?",
    answers: ["Rex","Sid","Hamm","George"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What specific creature does Indiana Jones hate?",
    answers: ["Spiders","Cockroaches","Snakes","Scorpions"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "In the 'Wizard of Oz', which witch wants Dorothy's ruby slippers?",
    answers: ["North","South","East","West"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "In Star Wars, which bird is associated with Han Solo‚Äôs 'Millenium' ship?",
    answers: ["Eagle","Hawk","Falcon","Albatross"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which of Forrest Gump‚Äôs body parts was wounded, thereby sending him home from Vietnam?",
    answers: ["Pinkie","Earlobe","Big toe","Buttock"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Which film contains the line 'this one time, at band camp...'?",
    answers: ["Wedding Crashers","Saving Silverman","American Pie","Dumb & Dumber"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which film contains the line 'I'm just a girl, standing in front of a boy, asking him to love her'?",
    answers: ["Four Weddings And A Funeral","Penelope","Pretty Woman","Notting Hill"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Who co-starred with Rik Mayall in the sitcom 'Bottom'?",
    answers: ["Martin Clunes","Ade Edmondson","Nigel Planer","Harry Enfield"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Who voiced the animated characters 'Dangermouse' and 'Count Duckula'?",
    answers: ["Ringo Starr","John Cleese","David Jason","Harry Enfield"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which band was Lionel Richie a member of?",
    answers: ["Amigas","Spectrums","Commodores","Ataris"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "How many states are in the USA?",
    answers: ["49","50","51","52"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Which of these US cities are not on the west coast",
    answers: ["San Diego","Los Angeles","Chicago","San Francisco"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "'Vilnius' is the capital of which country?",
    answers: ["Finland","Lithuania","Estonia","Ukraine"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What is the capital of Brazil?",
    answers: ["Brasilia","Rio de Janeiro","Sao Paulo","Belo Horizonte"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the capital of Brazil?",
    answers: ["Brasilia","Rio de Janeiro","Sao Paulo","Belo Horizonte"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What is the capital of Australia?",
    answers: ["Canberra","Melbourne","Sydney","Brisbane"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "The Prime Minister of Pakistan, Imran Khan, was previously famous for what?",
    answers: ["Cricket","Acting","Writing","Journalism"],
    answer: 0},
{question: "What nationality is former professional ice hockey player Wayne Gretzky?",
    answers: ["American","Canadian","Russian","Polish"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "How many holes are there in a full round of golf?",
    answers: ["9","12","15","18"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "What is the highest possible break in snooker?",
    answers: ["120","147","155","180"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Oliver Reed died during the making of which film?",
    answers: ["Braveheart","Gladiator","Alexander","300"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Piano Sonata No. 14, commonly known as the Moonlight Sonata, was written by...?",
    answers: ["Bach","Beethoven","Mozart","Chopin"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "How many millimetres are in a kilometre?",
    answers: ["1000","10,000","100,000","1,000,000"],
    answer: 3},
{question: "Who does James Bond work for?",
    answers: ["CIA","MI5","MI6","FBI"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is 2018 in roman numerals ?",
    answers: ["MCVIII","MMXVIII","XXMIII","MXCIII"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "What is 2018 in roman numerals?",
    answers: ["MCVIII","MMXVIII","XXMIII","MXCIII"],
    answer: 1},
{question: "Epsom, England is associated with...?",
    answers: ["Snooker","Cricket","Horse Racing","Rugby"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is Entomology associated with?",
    answers: ["Rocks","Human Behaviour","Insects","Glaciers"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is a 'John Dory'?",
    answers: ["Tractor","Beer","Fish","Dog"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "What is a 'John Dory'?",
    answers: ["Tractor","Beer","Fish","Dog"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which film is famous for the line 'Here's Johnny'?",
    answers: ["A Few Good Men","Scarface","The Shining","One Flew Over The Cuckoo's Nest"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Who played Lara Croft in the film adaptation of 'Tomb Raider'?",
    answers: ["Kate Winslet","Julia Roberts","Angelina Jolie","Sandra Bullock"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which musician played in the bands 'Cream', 'Derek & The Dominoes' and 'The Yardbirds'?",
    answers: ["Phil Collins","George Harrison","Eric Clapton","Paul McCartney"],
    answer: 2},
{question: "Which musician played in the bands 'The Jam', and 'The Style Council'?",
    answers: ["Bruce Foxton","Paul Weller","Joe Strummer","Johnny Ramone"],
    answer: 1}
];
